<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">

<properties>
  <entry key="explainBMR"><![CDATA[The first step is to calculate your basal metabolic rate.

Your basal metabolic rate is the number of calories you would burn if
you spent all day lying on the floor doing nothing.

You specified an age of {0} years, your height is {1} meters, and your
weight is {2} kilograms. You specified a biological gender of {3}.

Using the Mifflin St. Jeor formula, your basal metabolic rate should
be approximately {4} calories.

------------------------------------------------------------------------
]]></entry>

  <entry key="explainMaintenance"><![CDATA[The next step is to calculate your maintenance calorie count.

Your maintenance calorie count is the number of calories you require
to stay at your current weight, assuming that you do no exercise, and
that your level of daily non-exercise activity is {0}. This level of
activity multiplies your basal metabolic rate by {1}.

Based on the information given, your maintenance calorie count is
approximately {2} calories.

------------------------------------------------------------------------
]]></entry>

  <entry key="explainRecompCalories"><![CDATA[The next step is to calculate your target calorie count based on your goals.

You specified that your body recomposition goal is {0}.

Based on the information given, your body recomposition calorie count
should be approximately {1} calories.

------------------------------------------------------------------------
]]></entry>

  <entry key="explainMacros"><![CDATA[The last step is to work out what proportions of macronutrients you
should eat within your calorie limit of {0} calories.

Based on the information you specified about your body weight, gender,
body fat percentage, etc, you should eat approximately {1} of protein
per kilogram of body weight.

This means you should dedicate {2} of your total calories to protein,
which means eating {3}g of protein per day.

In order to ensure that your body has sufficient fat intake (ideally
saturated fats) to support muscle growth, you should dedicate {4} of
your total calories to fat. This means eating {5}g of fat per day.

Your remaining calories should be dedicated to carbohydrates. This
means you should dedicate {6} calories to carbohydrates, which means
eating {7} of carbohydrates per day.

------------------------------------------------------------------------
]]></entry>

  <entry key="explainSummary"><![CDATA[Summary

Total calories : {0}
Protein        : {1} g
Fat            : {2} g
Carbohydrates  : {3} g

You should recalculate these values every time your body weight
changes by ~5kg, or your desired weight changes cease.

------------------------------------------------------------------------
]]></entry>

  <entry key="surplus">increasing your body weight with a {0}% surplus</entry>
  <entry key="deficit">decreasing your body weight with a {0}% surplus</entry>
  <entry key="maintain">maintaining your body weight</entry>

</properties>